<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SpiritualTablet</string>
    <string name="hello_there">HELLO THERE! WELCOME BACK</string>
    <string name="log_in_to_continue">Log in to continue</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="mobile_no">Mobile No.</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="forger_password">Forger Password?</string>
    <string name="go">Go</string>
    <string name="new_user_sign_up">New User? SIGN UP</string>
    <string name="welcome">WELCOME</string>
    <string name="sign_up_to_start_your_journey">Sign up to start your journey</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account_login">Already have an account? LogIn</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="verify_mobile_no">Verify Mobile No</string>
    <string name="enter_verification_code_if_not_automatically_authenticated">Enter verification code if not automatically authenticated</string>
    <string name="verify">Verify</string>
    <string name="enter_otp">Enter OTP</string>
    <string name="audio">Audio</string>
    <string name="video">Video</string>
    <string name="books">Books</string>
    <string name="news_letters">News Letters</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log out</string>
    <string name="user_profile">User Profile</string>
    <string name="login">LogIn</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection0">No Internet Connection</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="telugu_books_list">Telugu Books List</string>
    <string name="list">List</string>
    <string name="english_books_list">English Books List</string>
    <string name="telugu_audio_list">Telugu Audio List</string>
    <string name="zero">0:00</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="introduction">Introduction</string>
    <string name="founder">Founder</string>
    <string name="founder_desc"><![CDATA[Dr. Gopala Krishna is a Medical Doctor from India who has 10 years of clinical experience and worked as DMO in Neuro Surgery, Pediatric and General Medicine department. He also has private practice in rural areas and worked as Medical Officer for Jarawa tribes in Andaman Islands. “Dr.Gopala Krishna” is also a spiritual scientist. He is an enlightened yogi, mystic and visionary who have dedicated himself to the elevation of the physical, mental, and spiritual well-being of people. He has shown a path for the people to attain natural joy and to live life with experience from their own inner nature through Pyramid power and Spiritual Tablets. His scientific approach towards spirituality and work towards the uplift of the humanity have received accolades in southern India, Malaysia, Singapore, Andaman, US & UK. Spiritual Tablets are the most profound, with greater intensity from his deep understanding and wisdom which can change the very core of the being. Belonging to no particular religion or tradition, “Spiritual Tablets” incorporates the modern person to the spiritual sciences. Spiritual Tablets, are the out pouring of his blissfulness, finds expression in the form of ceaseless offering to all beings. His life and Spiritual Tablets are invitation to connect with the divinity within us through individual transformation and welcomes the silent revolution of self realization.]]></string>
    <string name="introduction_desc">The world has become too materialistic and sadly we live in it, forgetting about nature. Society we live in got familiarize to mechanical life resultantly, lameness has spread in varied forms affecting a person\'s body, mind, spirit and social well-being that is leading to inadequacy of peace, pleasure and happiness. In order to decimate this \'Brahmastra\', a holistic health approach, was incorporated by name “SPIRITUAL TABLETS”. During the past 12 years a lot of research has been done and now, foundation which was started with an aim to “serve all” is a pride for the world. In the last 6 years, a group of spiritual counselors and volunteers, under the guidance of “Dr. Gopala Krishna” has developed 350 spiritual tablets in the form of text, audio and audio visuals. These Spiritual Concepts will change our internal belief system, that help us to transpose ourselves in order to open to the universe for its guidance in all circumstances. We conducted various training workshops which lead to the treasury of spiritual health care centers throughout the world, trained multiple cases teaching “meditation, spiritual counseling, spiritual guidance and spiritual tablets”.</string>
    <string name="history_origin"><![CDATA[History & Origin]]></string>
    <string name="histry_origin_desc">Pyramid Spiritual Societies Movement (PSSM) was founded by enlightened master “Brahmarshi Patriji” in the year 1990 with the objective, spiritual and harmonious living and bringing its benefits within the easy reach of all humanity, without any barriers of class, religion or region. Starting from its humble beginning with “The Kurnool Spiritual Society” in 1990, the Pyramid Meditation Movement is now spread by 2,000 independent and autonomous Pyramid Spiritual Societies involving millions of active members and volunteers across India, New Zealand, Australia, USA, UK, Singapore, Malaysia, UAE, Vietnam, Mauritius and Sri Lanka. The Pyramid Spiritual Societies Movement is non-religious, non-cult, non-profit voluntary organization with the mission to spread “Anapanasati Meditation, Vegetarianism and Pyramid Power” to everyone. “Dr. Gopala Krishna” is a medical doctor who started his journey of spiritual science in search of happiness and the truth, under the guidance of “Brahmarshi Patriji” and specially trained by grand master “Paul Vijay Kumar”. In this journey he got enlightened and realized that “Spiritual intellect is the root – physical health is the fruit”. He started sharing the same with his patients who approached him for medical treatment. As a part of this, he established spiritual health care centers and maintained them for ten years in different parts of India, also offered esteemed spiritual services as an ancillary to qualified treatment with the help of senior masters who are trained by him. Now we want to expand our services all over the world through offering franchise for establishing such centers. For this we established and registered a Non-Profit organization which is structured from centre in charge to the CEO.</string>

</resources>
